<xml>
   <item>
        <title>DaBs Must-Have 2 CoCoScope addons for DaButcher</title>
        <thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/83272.jpg</thumbnail>
        <link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=83272</link>
        <summary>Im so grateful to my great friends that made these 2 addon for me. Any of my followers can install these on their kodi setup to keep track of my videos. CocoDab runs on 19 only and DabScope runs on 18 and 19. Anyone can use these or modify them for their addons or channels. Kodi 18 and kodi 19</summary>
    </item>
	
	<item>
	<thumbnail>https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcS0PwiQvkxz2FrVvHvO_Cq90yy4_P2KZw_K9ohvJnLZ8TGBGIT3</thumbnail>
	<title>ICI RDI</title>
	<link>https://rcavlive.akamaized.net/hls/live/704026/canrdi/master.m3u8</link>
	<summary>ICI RDI</summary>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>CATCH-UP All</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/78263.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Catch-up-TV-and-More/plugin.video.catchuptvandmore/dev/resources/m3u/live_tv_ca.m3u</link>
		<summary>I show you how to install Turks 1.0.3 apk on a firestick lite. Here is some of the apps you might want
https://media-apps.com</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Télé-Québec</title>
		<thumbnail>resource://resource.images.catchuptvandmore/channels/ca/telequebec.png</thumbnail>
		<link>plugin://plugin.video.catchuptvandmore/resources/lib/channels/ca/telequebec/get_live_url/?item_id=telequebec</link>
		<summary>Télé-Québec</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>iptv frANCE</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/79891.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Catch-up-TV-and-More/plugin.video.catchuptvandmore/dev/resources/m3u/live_tv_fr.m3u</link>
		<summary>CATCH-UP FRANCE</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Must-Have Rogue 1 addon ShowCase</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/80132.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=80132</link>
		<summary>I was surprised how well Rogue 1 is laid out in a very user friendly way. It offers some Non-RD but majority of content needs a RD acct. The amount of 1 click content is amazing. It offers Movies, 4K,  Tv shows, MMA, WWE content and much more. The 1 click is very quick but offers a scraper package as a fallback. 
Narcacist Repo 
http://narcacist.com/repo/</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Stream Army repo and addons as of 2/21/2021</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/81367.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=81367</link>
		<summary>I show you how to install SA repo and install a couple current addons. I then show you how the pin system works and how to get a code.
Keep in mind Kodi 19 is BRAND new there WILL be BUGS. The addons willing to jump in the 19 waters early will have some hurdles to over come over the next few months. Thank you to those willing to do it so early in the Matrix life cycle.
A part I forgot to mention in my StreamArmy videos is a
 Pincode is 4 hours long. 
You could use it in different addons within that 4 hours.
URLs
Repo
http://streamarmy.co.uk/repo</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Nixgate repo and Seren addon</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/81369.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=81369</link>
		<summary>I will walk you through install of Nixgate repo and install of Seren. I then add scrapers and test a couple movies. Seems to be working great and keep in mind with Seren you need a premium service ( Rd, Prem, All-Debrid, etc ).  Nixgate has this 19 ready but as with any new code there may be bugs to iron out. He is on the job and will sort them out asap. I want to thank him for his continued work on this project. 
		Repo
 https://nixgates.github.io/packages
Provider Package
http://bit.ly/a4kScrapers</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - TheOath addon v2 With text edits</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/81451.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=81451</link>
		<summary>This is a exodus base that has been converted to py 3 to work in Kodi 19. Runs great for free and Premium links. This addon is not talked about often but is a solid addon for folks that love Exodus look at feel. Thank you to the dev and his/her work on this project. If the dev is on Telegram hit me up
		https://host505.github.io/</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Dabs Matrix 19 Help - Adult video addon Cumination</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/81471.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=81471</link>
		<summary>*This addon is for people 18 or older **
This addon was suggested to me from a very active member of the Kodi community. This addon links to 72 web sites at the time of this video. It offers a way to Favorite certain videos and also make custom lists. Hope you enjoy the addon and I will be on the look out for others.
Cumination addon from the Dobbelina Repo
Extra feature I missed.. This offers the feature to DOWNLOAD most videos into a folder within the addon
https://dobbelina.github.io/</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Adult addon XXX-O-Dus</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/81472.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=81472</link>
		<summary>**This addon is for People Over the Age 18**
Nemzzy has done it again with another 19 conversion of a favorite Kodi addon. xxxodus is now 19 compat. and ready to install on your Matrix setup. This links to dozens and dozens of web sites bringing you shorts, clips, movies, live cams, fetish, hentai, gay, pictures and much more. This is a great addon for those wanting adult content. Much thx to Nemzzy for getting so much content for kodi 19 users.
A part I forgot to mention in my StreamArmy videos is a
 Pincode is 4 hours long. 
You could use it in different addons within that 4 hours.
http://streamarmy.co.uk/repo/</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - WatchNixToons2 addon</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/81521.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=81521</link>
		<summary>This was a favorite addon for kodi users for years. It now has been ported over to 19 and most things seem to be working. At the moment I have not found it on an official repo but Slam has added the zip to a server so folks can install it. If I find the real repo for it I will add to these notes. Thank you to the folks that converted this to 19, those working on modules and scripts that make this work and Slam for placing it in a place people can get it.
https://slamiousbuilds.com/19repo/zips/</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - EntertainMe addon by StreamArmy</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/81523.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=81523</link>
		<summary>This is a great addon that DOES NOT NEED Real Debrid. It pulls links from a single web site. It offers free tv shows and movies. It does require a pin that is valid for 4 hours in any of the addons hosted by streamarmy. Thank you to Nemzzy for busting his butt to update all these addons inside of SA repo. This was no little job.
http://streamarmy.co.uk/repo/</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
        <title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - FDJ.HD addon by FrenchDJ</title>
        <thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/81632.jpg</thumbnail>
        <link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=81632</link>
        <summary>This was a addon loved by many people on 18 and now its made its way to Matrix. This addon offers Music concerts, DJ sets and a big docs section. You will need to make sure you have Youtube addon 6.x.x +matrix installed. Thank you to FrenchDJ for getting this on Python3 as quick as you did. 
Link to repo
https://alivegr.net/master/</summary>
    </item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Revolution addon by Captain Jerk</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/81689.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=81689</link>
		<summary>Some of you might have used this as a kodi 18 addon and liked it. Well here is the Kodi 19 release of it. It uses Open scrapers, has free links as well as Debrid links, Trakt, and Orion accts can used in this addon. For forks that prefer a exodus style layout with those features you might want to check this out. Repo
https://dejavurepo.github.io/</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - MP3 Streams addon edits from Diggz and Slam</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/81902.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=81902</link>
		<summary>OK this addon has been converted and does play songs. The server that its hosted at is getting hammered so as you see in video some times it was slow to respond. So be patient. A few bugs I noticed and this not to knock on the guys work but so ppl dont comment this or that dont work. 
Again, Thank you to Diggz and Slam for their work on this but just tossing out things I noticed so users dont think its their install thats messed up.  
Link
https://slamiousbuilds.com/19repo/zips/</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Shadow 19 update is out of the shadows</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/81993.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=81993</link>
		<summary>Its finally here. Shadow 19 Kinda.. Its a release that works in 18 and 19 , same zip. :) This is a awesome addon and I know many people that moved to 19 were missing it. As I said in the video Kodi 19 has issues and will until the Kodi team sort out the bugs. Well same goes for addons that have moved to 19. There will be bugs and errors as people test and try different combo of things to cause the error. So be patient or just stay on 18.9. That Kodi release and library of addons runs great. I want to thank the Dev of Shadow for lurking in the shadows and surprising us with this update.
I will post repos that house shadow.
https://team-crew.github.io/</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Deccan Delight Hindi, Tamil, Telugu and others</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/82212.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=82212</link>
		<summary>This addon is very unique in that it fits a need for People that live in India or countries close to find content they looking for. Most popular addons we all know about have a VERY hard time this content. Well Gujal has packed a ton of web sites into this 1 addon. Big thanks to Gujal and the work he/she does in community. Let me know what yall think of this addon
Link to repo
https://gujal00.github.io/</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - SportsHD addon by Bugatchino</title>
		<thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/82700.jpg</thumbnail>
		<link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=82700</link>
		<summary>This came out last week but just got time to show it to you. Sports addons are few and far between on K19 so this is a rare gem. It works great and can give you SOME LIVE SPORTS. This WILL NOT have every sport or multiple links. It has a list updated daily of events it was able to find. You will see in the video the layout and list of sports for time i created the video. Much Thanks to Bug for releasing this so some sport fans might watch their team.
URL
https://bugatsinho.github.io/repo</summary>
	</item>

	<item>
        <title>Dabs Matrix 19 help - MP3 Streams PART 2 by Slam</title>
        <thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/82735.jpg</thumbnail>
        <link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=82735</link>
        <summary>This is a updated video on the features and fixes since my 1st video when mp3 streams was released. Slam has done great work to get this up and running even better. Download, create many of your own  playlist Lp and songs. Runs very good now and Many thanks to Slam for this update.
https://slamiousbuilds.com/19repo/zips/repository.slam19/</summary>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Cloud 9 Sports addon From DejaVu repo</title>
        <thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/82775.jpg</thumbnail>
        <link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=82775</link>
        <summary>Man oh man I get asked daily about sports addons in KOdi 19. Finally we have it. A addon that offers a BUNCH of channels for sports fans. Big thanks to the folks at Dejavu repo for this great release. 
Link
https://dejavurepo.github.io/</summary>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - DejaVu Again addon from DJV repo</title>
        <thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/82780.jpg</thumbnail>
        <link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=82780</link>
        <summary>Here is a addon packed with direct links which most need Rd. 4k, movies, classics, tv, new stuff, kids and even sports. This thing is a all in one with all your bases covered. This works off the shadow base so you can use on 18 or 19 and even use shadow to find content not in the direct links. Hats off to the work on this one. 
URL repo
https://dejavurepo.github.io/</summary>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - The Boys addon from Chains repo</title>
        <thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/82781.jpg</thumbnail>
        <link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=82781</link>
        <summary>We have a addon that will work in 18 or 19 and has 3 great sets of lists. Ghost, Chains and Wasteland have been added to a shadow base so you get the best of all worlds. This offer Non-Rd, RD, 4k, sports, replays and much more. Look to these guys to continue to kick out great content.  Thanks for their hard work and keep truckin ahead.
Links for repos
http://thechains24.com/ChainsRepo/
https://team-crew.github.io/</summary>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Venom addon is NOT GONE !!</title>
        <thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/82788.jpg</thumbnail>
        <link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=82788</link>
        <summary>Wow was I wrong.. I thought I read a reddit post that Fen would be staying but Venom was done. After installing and scraping for content I was off by a mile. This thing is FAST !!!! They seemed to have streamlined the scrapers to only be using the ones responding quick. Two thumbs up for this work. Kodi 19 Matrix keeps adding addons
Repo URL
https://123venom.github.io</summary>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Fen addon by Tikipeter</title>
        <thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/82834.jpg</thumbnail>
        <link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=82834</link>
        <summary>This addon is not new by any means but its been converted to work in 19 and it seems amazingly fast with features and settings that can go on for days. You can use Rd, Pm, Ad, Furk, easynews as well as scanning folders,drives or Nas on your network. The HELP documentation is top notch. Im a guy that likes to try things and change settings to make it work better for me. Well with the docs it can help you to understand what things you may want to tweak. A Major wow on the work that went into FEN and hats off for the total experience of the addon. Kodi 19 matrix https://123venom.github.io</summary>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - 4k addon by NaRcAcIsT</title>
        <thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/83089.jpg</thumbnail>
        <link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=83089</link>
        <summary>Want 4k ???????
This was a popular addon in kodi 18 now its on kodi 19. The speed of 19 and direct links are golden. You will need RD, PM or AD for this one to pull links. As I state in the video if you get error on pulling link its most likely a authorize issue. The search feature is awesome in this. It can search the DB so quick and give you links to it. No waiting for scrapers this is direct fast links. 
Again 4K content ONLY!
http://narcacist.com/repo/
https://ezzer-mac.com/repo/</summary>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Rogue 1 addon by Numpty's</title>
        <thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/83096.jpg</thumbnail>
        <link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=83096</link>
        <summary>The FORCE RUNS STRONG IN THIS ONE.. :)
This is a Jen addon  from kodi 18 that has used shadow 19 base to add their custom playlists. There is a lot of content and I made a video a few weeks back on the 18 Ver. This offers Direct (RD) links, free links, TV, Movies shadow scraper package, standup, musicals, kids, sports replays and much more. This is quick and runs very smooth. Great work by Numpty's and this gives folks another option for kodi 19 matrix
http://narcacist.com/repo/</summary>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>DaBs Matrix 19 Help - Black Lightning addon by cMaN</title>
        <thumbnail>https://ws0.cocoscope.com/thumbnails/83094.jpg</thumbnail>
        <link>https://www.cocoscope.com/watch?v=83094</link>
        <summary>Well well well.. Asgard has found its way to Kodi 19 in disguise ..:D
Black lightning addon is fast and offers Premium direct links, free link, kids, sports replays, old movies, shadow scraper package and much more. This is a AIO addon. This being on kodi 19 gives people a great option on finding content. Two thumbs up to work cman did on this one. Works on kodi 18 or kodi 19 
http://cmanbuilds.com/repo/
http://narcacist.com/repo/</summary>
    </item>
</xml>
